Privacy Policy for Legcord - Discord Client Effective Date: 25.05.2023 Thank you for choosing Legcord, a Discord client that prioritizes privacy and security. This Privacy Policy explains how Legcord handles your personal information and your interactions with Discord and Cloudflare. Please read this policy carefully to understand how your data is handled when using Legcord. 1. Collection of Personal Information Legcord itself does not collect any personal information from its users. We do not store, transmit, or process any user data directly on our servers. 2. Discord Legcord relies on the Discord API and services to function. When you use Legcord, Discord may collect and process your personal information as described in Discord's Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review Discord's Privacy Policy to understand how they collect, use, and disclose your personal information. 3. Cloudflare Legcord also utilizes Cloudflare's services to enhance security and provide a reliable user experience. Cloudflare may collect and process your personal information according to its own Privacy Policy. We recommend reviewing Cloudflare's Privacy Policy to understand their data practices. 4. User Consent By using Legcord, you acknowledge and consent to Discord and Cloudflare collecting and processing your personal information as described in their respective privacy policies. Legcord is not responsible for the privacy practices of Discord or Cloudflare. 5. Security Measures Legcord is committed to safeguarding your personal information. We take appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your data against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that no method of data transmission over the internet or electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 6. Third-Party Services and Websites Legcord may contain links to third-party services or websites that are not operated or controlled by us. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party services or websites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those third parties to understand their data practices. 7. Children's Privacy Legcord is not intended for use by individuals under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe that we have inadvertently collected personal information from a child under 13, please contact us immediately at support@legcord.app, and we will take appropriate steps to remove the information. 8. Changes to the Privacy Policy We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our practices or for legal, regulatory, or operational reasons. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the updated Privacy Policy on our website or through other reasonable means. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy for any updates. 9. Contact Us If you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy or your personal information, please contact us at support@legcord.app By using Legcord, you agree to the terms and conditions outlined in this Privacy Policy.
